infotoday.com 2019-07-29

# ITI Privacy and Cookies Policy

_Updated: 18 April 2019._  
Questions or comments about this privacy policy may be directed to: **[privacy@infotoday.com](mailto:privacy@infotoday.com)**.

The various Information Today, Inc. websites include: information about our company; subscription, sales, and delivery of content for periodicals, books, and directories that we publish; and conferences that we organize. 

These websites are maintained and operated by Information Today, Inc. (ITI), 143 Old Marlton Pike, Medford, NJ 08055, Phone: 609-654-6266. Send comments or suggestions about these sites to: **[webmaster@infotoday.com](mailto:webmaster@infotoday.com)**. 

For each visitor to our websites, our Web servers log the IP address of the computer the visitor is using to view our Web pages, as well as the referring URL.  We routinely collect information on what pages they access or visit. This information is used for internal review and to improve the content of our websites. We only collect personal information (including contact and email information) that is willingly provided by visitors to our websites. 

The Information Today/Plexus Publishing Online Store website (hosted by Yahoo!, at **[**bookstore.infotoday.com**](http://bookstore.infotoday.com/)** ) collects information about customers, including purchase and contact information, and securely provides it to Information Today, Inc., which is solely responsible for its use.  We only use that information to complete a transaction requested by a customer. Every transaction conducted at the Information Today Online Store website is encrypted for the customers' protection.  The Yahoo! privacy policy is available at **<http://docs.yahoo.com/info/privacy/>**. 

### **_Your information/Personal Data_**

Each time you request information from us, register to attend one of ITI's conferences, subscribe to an electronic newsletter, sign up for an online event (Webinar), submit a proposal to speak at one of ITI's conferences, subscribe to an online service or print publication, register to view/download premium content on one of our websites, or make a purchase from our online store, we request certain personal data, including: Full Name, Mailing/Postal Address, Email Address, Phone Number(s), Employer, and Job Title. We may also ask for additional employment demographic information including industry sector, number of employees, and company income. When you submit a proposal to speak at a conference, we may also request biographical information as well as your history of speaking at other conferences. 

We use personal data you submit to us to complete transactions such as conference registrations, subscription fulfillment, or communication regarding requests to speak at a conference. We may share your personal data with sponsors of our conferences, premium content, and webinars, so that they may extend you offers of interest, in accordance with their own privacy policies. 

We may also include you in our email mailing lists. We will request your consent to send you email via these lists. We may use these mailing lists or your information or for internal marketing and promotional purposes to occasionally notify you of Information Today, Inc. products and services we think will interest you. We may also send you email on behalf of our sponsors. If you don't wish to receive such notifications and offers from ITI, you can request to be removed from our mailing lists. Every email message sent to mailing lists maintained by Information Today, Inc. contains a link to automatically unsubscribe from the list or lists, to which the email was sent.

### _GDPR_

For the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), our lawful bases for processing the personal data of EU individuals are _Contract_ , _Legitimate Interest_ , and _Consent_. In the case of accepting your registration and payment to attend one of our conferences, or if you subscribe to one of our publications, we process your personal data in order to fulfil our contractual obligations to you. In some cases we use legitimate interest as a lawful basis for processing your data, including sharing of your personal data with sponsors of our premium content, webinars, and conferences so that they may extend you offers of interest. We define ‘legitimate interest’ as providing you with additional useful information on related products and services that we or our sponsors provide, based on the interests you have expressed by downloading sponsored premium content or viewing sponsored webinars. If you register to attend or speak at one of our UK-based conferences, you will be asked for your consent to receive related information from third parties, including conference sponsors and exhibitors. 

You have the right to access, update, delete, or request a copy of the personal data we hold about you. If you want it to be updated, or removed from our systems, please contact us via email (to **[privacy@infotoday.com](mailto:privacy@infotoday.com)** ), telephone (609-654-6266), fax (609-654-4309), or in writing (Information Today, Inc., 143 Old Marlton Pike, Medford, NJ 08055-8750). 

Information Today, Inc. is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). Information Today, Inc. is required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.   

### _EU-U.S. Privacy Shield_

Information Today, Inc. complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Information Today, Inc. has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit **<https://www.privacyshield.gov/>**

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Information Today, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Information Today, Inc. via email at: [ **privacy@infotoday.com**](mailto:privacy@infotoday.com)

Information Today, Inc. has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning data transferred from the EU. 

In cases of onward transfers of data, received pursuant to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield, Information Today, Inc. is potentially liable.

The Privacy Shield Framework provides the option for an EU individual to invoke binding arbitration to determine whether Information Today, Inc. has violated its obligations under the Privacy Shield Principles as to that individual and whether any such violation remains fully or partially unremedied.

###  **__**_Social buttons_

On many of the pages of our websites you will see ‘social buttons’. These enable users to share or bookmark the web pages. There may be buttons for: Twitter, Google +, Facebook's ‘Like’, LinkedIn's ‘Share’, YouTube, or others. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of Information Today, Inc.'s. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on our websites. 

So if you click on any of these buttons, these sites will be registering that action and may use that information. In some cases these sites will be registering the fact that you are visiting our websites, and the specific pages you are on, even if you don’t click on the button if you are logged into their services, like Google and Facebook. You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information.

### **_Cookies_**

A cookie is a small text file, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your computer or other access device from our servers, or from the servers of our third-party partners. 

The various Information Today, Inc. websites use different types of cookies. 

> By using our websites, you consent to our use of cookies on your computer or other access device, in accordance with this cookie policy.
> 
> If you do not consent to our use of cookies, then you should either not use our websites, or use your browser in anonymous mode (“Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” in Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari). 
> 
> Information on how you can delete, disable, or control cookies for most Web browsers is available at [www.AllAboutCookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/). 
> 
> Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our websites.

Our websites that offer access to White Papers, Webinars, and other premium content and online events use cookies to store registration information, so that website visitors are remembered, and do not need to supply that information upon each visit. 

The Literary Market Place and American Library Directory websites use cookies to maintain user sessions and log out users after a specific length of time. 

The Information Today Online Store website uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about customers. For more information about the use of cookies on the Information Today/Plexus Publishing Online Store website, see **<http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/cookies/details.html>**. 

Information Today, Inc. uses certain third-party partner companies that also send cookies to your computer/device via your web browser.

We use **Google Analytics** , a popular web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to count the number of visitors to our websites, and helps us to analyze how users use our websites. It tells us things such as the typical length of stay on the site or the average number of pages a user views. User data is all anonymous.

You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at **<http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html>**

We use **Google's DoubleClick for Publishers** to serve ads on our websites. These cookies are very similar to the Google Analytics cookie described above, but are specific to the display of advertising on our websites. User data is anonymous.

**Google AdSense** cookies are used by Google to report to us how certain ads shown on our websites are performing. User data is all anonymous.

You can find out more generally about Google and its policies and principles as regards advertising at **<http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/>**

Some of the ads you may see on our websites are customized based on predictions about your interests generated from your visits over time and across different websites. This type of ad customization - sometimes called “online behavioral” or “interest-based” advertising - is accomplished by the use of cookies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used, [**click here**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). 

* * *
